A message the Lord said I should give to my African Continent:
No African country can succeed alone.
Africans need each other to develop.
Tell your neighbour.
[Africans need each other to develop.]
West Africa needs Southern Africa to develop.
Southern Africa needs West Africa to develop.
North Africa needs East Africa to develop
and East Africa needs North Africa to develop.
No one is self-sufficient.
We cannot do without each other.
Everyone has a contribution.
Whether you are poor, rich or an immigrant,
everyone has a contribution for the development of Africa, at the level we are now.
Dear Africans, we should not let other fellow Africans feel unwelcome to our countries.
With regard to the issue of illegal immigrants, drugs and other crimes,
our duty is to inform law enforcement agencies.
That is our duty - to give them useful information about issues like that.
In our respective countries, our duty is to inform law enforcement agencies.
It is only when they fail to carry out their duty that we citizens can lawfully protest.
I want to show you a little video before I continue talking.
There is no country in Africa that is not involved in what you are about to watch.
What is the cause?
It's because Africa has neglected her youth
Africa has neglected her youth.
The youth - they have neglected them.
Africa has abandoned the youth to themselves
whereas tomorrow's Africa is the youth.
But we have neglected them - that is the cause of all this frustration.
When I think about the future of Africa, I have sleepless nights.
Please, can you play this cassette for me - please, let's watch.
In the mediterranean, off the coast of Libya,
this unstable fishing boat is overloaded with migrants and refugees.
So there is a horrible inevitability in what is about to happen.
The boat is starting to tilt.
Then the situation becomes so much worse.
Many jump into the waters of the mediterranean before the boat completely capsizes.
Moments later, it is completely overturned
Scores swam away from the shipwreck
but five people were found dead in the water.
But this man and 561 others were rescued.
They are now safe but the scenes of utter desperation we witnessed this time last year,
they constantly repeated themselves.
Important Message For ALL AFRICANS!!! | T.B. Joshua
They are your children; they are youth of Africa.
All - they are youth of Africa.
There is no country in Africa that is not represented there - all.
These are your children that claim they have travelled outside the country.
Many of them are there - looking for green pastures.
Africa has neglected her youth.
Africa has abandoned the youth to themselves.
Africa has failed to provide green pastures.
When I think about the future of Africa, I have sleepless nights.
Within Africa, if we are now fighting ourselves,
look at what is happening in other continents concerning Africa.
Within continents, there is fight among the youth.
Everything looks gloomy, frustrating, hopeless, dark, darksome, dull and sunless.
Africa, unite!
No African country can succeed alone; we need each other to develop.
So, if we cannot understand ourselves within Africa,
do you mean they will understand us in other continents?
I was so troubled, and the Lord gave me a word:
I want to volunteer myself, and I know God has touched many Africans.
I know as I am talking, God has touched many Africans and
many Africans that are in a position to help and I know many of them are crying.
I am at your service.
I will not only sit in the church alone.
You will learn that I have travelled for a meeting with people
that are ready to talk about the challenges ahead.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Yes, look at the ministry.
All countries, races are inside the church.
God said, "No, I release you".
He said he has touched many people that are in the position of honour and authority.
They are ready. Let's come together.
Let's talk about the youth that have been neglected.
They have been neglected.
They have been abandoned to themselves.
No provision for our youth.
When you are counting the best universities in the world,
you will hardly see a single university from Africa among 1 to 500.
There is no single African university.
Can you see the decadence?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The technology is zero.
You are flying to Dubai, you are flying to Turkey, you are flying to New York.
When are they flying into your country?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Look at your age - are you not going to witness that transformation
when Africa will become a centre, where people will begin to discover themselves?
You are getting old.
Now your children, where is that future for them?
They have been abandoned.
Because they have been abandoned, that is the cause of frustration.
Frustration can make anyone to do anything.
When you realise you are a graduate and there is no job and
you are looking at your age and wondering where you are going
and every day things are becoming worse - it is frustration.
Dear Africa, we should not let other fellow Africans feel unwelcome to our countries.
Tell your neighbour.
Fellow Africans, we should not let other fellow Africans feel unwelcome to our countries.
Again!
[Fellow Africans, we should not let other fellow Africans feel unwelcome to our countries.]
No African country can succeed, can develop alone.
When it now comes to the issue of people taking drugs to a country or crimes,
our duty is to work with law enforcement by giving them useful information
about these people that are doing this.
That is our duty.
But if they now fail to do so, then lawfully we can protest.
Other nations are now laying bans on immigrants;
definitely, we Africans should awake and rescue our people.
If there is ban on immigrants, definitely, this is the time we should awake.
What can we do to rescue our people?
Because these immigrants we are talking about, 90% are Africans.
So they are coming back home.
And many of them are home already.
Unemployment.
And millions are coming to join unemployment at home.
Where is the peace?
No matter how much you are blessed, you can never have peace
if people around you are suffering.
RV: Mel Flowers 27/04/2019